Guide to the Robert Fitzgerald Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Correspondence, 1902-1986; Series I; 22.52; (54 boxes)
  - GENERAL CORRESPONDENCE
    - Harris, Clark, Green, Piper, and Robinson, 1970-71 (Box 15, Folder 595)
    - Harris, Russell, 1954-68 (Box 15, Folder 596)
    - Hartman, Geoffrey, 1952, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 597)
      Includes carbon copy of poems
    - The Harvard Advocate, 1966-81, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 598)
    - Harvard Alumni Association, 1958-78 (Box 16, Folder 599-600)
    - Harvard Business School, 1981-84, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 601)
    - Harvard Club of New York City, 1936-85, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 602)
    - Harvard College (1780-). Class of 1933, 1970-82 (Box 16, Folder 603)
    - Harvard College. Committee on Undergraduate Education, 1978-79, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 604)
    - Harvard College Library, 1965-83, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 605-606)
      Includes position description
    - Harvard Cooperative Society, 1971, 1974 (Box 16, Folder 607)
    - The Harvard Crimson, 1979 Dec 11 (Box 16, Folder 608)
    - Harvard Dramatic Club, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 609)
    - Harvard Magazine, 1974-84 (Box 16, Folder 610)
    - Harvard Medical School, 1970, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 611)
    - Harvard Real Estate, Inc., 1975-81, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 612)
    - Harvard Ukrainian Research Institute, 1975-76 (Box 16, Folder 613)
    - Harvard University, 1929-84, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 614-615)
    - Harvard University. Administrative Board, 1969-79 (Box 16, Folder 616)
    - Harvard University. Board of Overseers, 1969-81 (Box 16, Folder 617)
    - Harvard University. Committee on Medieval Studies, 1978-79 (Box 16, Folder 618)
    - Harvard University. Dean's Office, 1932-83 (Box 16, Folder 619)
    - Harvard University. Dept. of Classics, 1964-81 (Box 16, Folder 620)
      Includes copies of letters to Ihor Sevcenko from Homer A. Thompson, Linos Politis, Henry Rosovsky, M. Manousakas and Peter Topping
    - Harvard University. Dept. of Comparative Literature, 1963-84, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 621)
    - Harvard University. Dept. of English, 1964-72 (Box 16, Folder 622-623)
      Includes copies of third party correspondence and enclosures
    - Harvard University. Dept. of English, 1972-81, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 624-631)
    - Harvard University. Dept. of Philosophy, 1978 Mar 20 (Box 17, Folder 632)
    - Harvard University. Dunster House, 1966-81, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 633)
    - Harvard University. Employees' Credit Union, 1972-77, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 634)
    - Harvard University. Faculty of Arts and Sciences, 1970-80, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 635)
    - Harvard University. Freshman Seminar Program, 1979-81 (Box 17, Folder 636)
    - Harvard University. Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, 1968-82 (Box 17, Folder 637)
    - Harvard University. Housing Office, 1968-77, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 638)
    - Harvard University. Loeb Drama Center, 1964-77 (Box 17, Folder 639)
    - Harvard University. The Memorial Church, 1969-79 (Box 17, Folder 640)
    - Harvard University. News Office, 1971-81 (Box 17, Folder 641)
      Includes biographical sketches of RSF
    - Harvard University. Nieman Foundation, 1969-75 (Box 17, Folder 642)
    - Harvard University. Office of Fiscal Services, 1974-80 (Box 17, Folder 643)
    - Harvard University. Office of the Comptroller, 1966-73 (Box 18, Folder 644)
    - Harvard University. Personnel Office, 1967-81 (Box 18, Folder 645)
      Includes copies of letters to Prudential Insurance and enclosures
    - Harvard University. President's Office, 1965-83, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 646)
    - Harvard University. Press, 1965-80 (Box 18, Folder 647)
    - Harvard University. Signet Society, 1969-80, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 648)
    - Harvard University. Society of Fellows, 1970-81 (Box 18, Folder 649)
    - [Harvard University Students], 1970-81, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 650-657)
    - [Harvard University Students/Letters of Recommendation], 1973-81 (Box 18, Folder 658-659)
    - Harvard University. University Health Services, 1976-81 (Box 18, Folder 660)
      See also: Personal Papers, Medical Records, Box 96, folder 3398
    - Harvard-Radcliffe Catholic Student Center, 1966-71 (Box 18, Folder 661)
    - Harvill Press Ltd., 1983-85 (Box 19, Folder 662)
    - Hasencleaver, Walter, 1954 Jun 14 (Box 19, Folder 663)
    - Hasty Pudding Club, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 664)
    - Hatch, Nathan, 1977 Nov 21 (Box 19, Folder 665)
    - Hatfield, Henry Caraway, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 666)
    - Haviaras, Stratis, 1977, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 667)
    - Hawkins, Erick, 1947-48 (Box 19, Folder 668)
    - Hayes, Richard, 1953 (Box 19, Folder 669)
    - Heaney, Seamus, 1975-83, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 670)
    - Hecht, Anthony, 1969-83 (Box 19, Folder 671)
      Includes letters to Hecht from Henri Cole
    - Hecht, Roger, 1957-79 (Box 19, Folder 672)
    - Heckenberg, R. G., 1958-66 (Box 19, Folder 673-674)
    - Heffernan, Thomas, 1976-81 (Box 19, Folder 675)
      Includes copy of letter from Heffernan to John V. Kelleher
    - Hegarty, Charles M., 1971-72 (Box 19, Folder 676)
    - Hegler Institute, 1975 Jan 31 (Box 19, Folder 677)
    - Heilman, Robert, 1982 Jun 25 (Box 19, Folder 678)
    - Heinemann (Firm), 1962-63 (Box 19, Folder 679)
    - Heist, Jerry, 1966-71 (Box 19, Folder 680)
    - Hellerstein, David, 1982 Apr 29 (Box 19, Folder 681)
      Includes copy of article
    - Hellman, Lillian, 1975-84, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 682)
    - Helm, Levon; Helm, Libby, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 683)
    - Helmling, Steven, 1975 Feb (Box 19, Folder 684)
    - Henderson, Charles, 1975 Dec 3 (Box 19, Folder 685)
    - Hendricks, Geoffrey; Hendricks, Bici, 1962-69 (Box 19, Folder 686)
    - Herbert, Thomas Walter; Herbert, Jean, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 687)
    - Herder and Herder, 1969 Aug 11 (Box 19, Folder 688)
    - Hering, Frank E., 1949, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 689)
    - Hersey, Barbara, 1984, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 690)
    - Hersey, John, 1979-85 (Box 19, Folder 691)
    - Higgins, Judith, 1973 May 25 (Box 19, Folder 692)
    - Higgins, Mary Jane, 1977 Aug 25 (Box 19, Folder 693)
    - Highet, Gilbert, 1949-50 (Box 19, Folder 694)
      Includes notes on translation of Oedipus
    - Higonnet, René, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 695)
    - Hill, Julia Yancy, [ca. 1929-30] (Box 19, Folder 696)
    - Hills, Roderick; Hills, Carla, 1969-70 (Box 19, Folder 697)
      Includes copies of lease and checks
    - Hillyer, Robert Silliman, 1947-49 (Box 19, Folder 698)
    - Hobson, Wilder, 1955 Jun 28 (Box 19, Folder 699)
    - Hoehn, Matthew, 1949 Jun 24 (Box 19, Folder 700)
    - Hofer, Philip, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 701)
    - Hoffman, Daniel, 1975-84 (Box 19, Folder 702)
    - Hogan, James C., 1976-80 (Box 19, Folder 703)
    - Hollander, John, 1964-78, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 704)
    - Hollander, Robert, 1966-80 (Box 20, Folder 705)
      Includes copies of letters to Hollander from Stuart McDougal
      See also: McDougal, Stuart, Box 24, folder 902
    - Holt, Reinhart, and Winston, Inc., 1963-72 (Box 20, Folder 706)
      Includes contract
    - Holzberger, William G., 1978 (Box 20, Folder 707)
    - Homalka, Florence, 1956 Dec 14 (Box 20, Folder 708)
    - Homiak, Marcia, 1982-84 (Box 20, Folder 709)
    - Honig, Edwin, 1975-84 (Box 20, Folder 710)
    - Horizon, 1965, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 711)
    - Houghton Library, 1974, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 712)
    - Houghton Mifflin Company, 1958-84 (Box 20, Folder 713-714)
    - The Hound and Horn, 1932-33 (Box 20, Folder 715)
    - Houston, Peyton, 1935 Mar 5 (Box 20, Folder 716)
    - Hovanessian, Diana der, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 717)
    - Howarth, William, 1983 Sep 15 (Box 20, Folder 718)
    - Howe, Irving, 1978 Sep 27 (Box 20, Folder 719)
    - Howe, Parkman, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 720)
      Includes biographical note
    - Howes, Barbara, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 721)
    - The Hudson Review, 1955-82 (Box 20, Folder 722)
    - Hugh, Dudley, 1947, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 723)
    - Hussey, Anne, 1976-80 (Box 20, Folder 724)
    - Huxtable, Andrew, 1967 Sep 18 (Box 20, Folder 725)
    - Hyde, James Nevins; Hyde, Peggy, 1931-80, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 726-727)
    - Hyman, Stanley Edgar, 1966 Jan 21 (Box 20, Folder 728)
    - Hynson, Garrett P., 1930-32, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 729)
    - "I" General, 1954-64 (Box 20, Folder 730)
    - Ignatius, David, 1971 May (Box 20, Folder 731)
    - Illuminations, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 732)
      Includes copy of journal
    - Indiana University, Bloomington, 1957 Mar 9 (Box 20, Folder 733)
    - Indiana University, Bloomington. College of Arts and Sciences, 1976 Aug 13 (Box 20, Folder 734)
    - Indiana University, Bloomington. Dept. of Comparative Literature, 1961-77 (Box 20, Folder 735)
    - Indiana University, Bloomington. School of Arts and Letters, 1951-72 (Box 20, Folder 736)
    - Indiana University Press, 1964-71 (Box 20, Folder 737)
    - Ingram, Bowen, 1972 Nov 25 (Box 20, Folder 738)
    - Ingram, Forrest, 1966 Jun 11 (Box 20, Folder 739)
    - The Ingram Merrill Foundation, 1965-83 (Box 20, Folder 740)
    - Institut Florimont, 1960, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 741)
    - Institut International - Jacques Maritain, 1979 Jan 29 (Box 20, Folder 742)
    - Institute for Advanced Study (Princeton, N.J.), 1980-83 (Box 20, Folder 743)
    - Intercollegiate Studies Institute, 1974 Jan 17 (Box 20, Folder 744)
    - International Biographical Centre, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 745)
    - International Committee on English in the Liturgy, 1966 Apr 12 (Box 20, Folder 746)
    - International Rescue Committee, 1979, 1981 (Box 20, Folder 747)
    - The Iowa Review, 1984 Apr 30 (Box 20, Folder 748)
    - Irish American Cultural Institute, 1976 Feb 10 (Box 20, Folder 749)
    - The Irish Times, 1959 Jun 10 (Box 20, Folder 750)
    - Irish Tourist Board, 1959 Jun 17 (Box 20, Folder 751)
    - Irvine, Maurice, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 752)
    - Isard, Walter, 1968-69 (Box 21, Folder 753)
    - [Italian Students], 1960 Aug (Box 21, Folder 754)
    - Ivancic, Maria, 1949-66, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 755)
    - "J" General, 1953-84, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 756)
    - The J. Robert Oppenheimer Fund, 1977-78 (Box 21, Folder 757)
    - Jackson, Bruce, 1974-75 (Box 21, Folder 758)
    - Jackson, J. David, 1979 Jan (Box 21, Folder 759)
    - Jackson, Katherine, 1979-80 (Box 21, Folder 760)
    - Jackson, "Kit" Townsend, 1939-40, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 761)
    - Jackson, Laura (Riding), 1937-77, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 762-763)
      Includes copy of third party letter
    - Jackson, Schuyler, 1938-75 (Box 21, Folder 764)
      See also: Jackson, Laura (Riding), Box 21, folders 762-763
    - Jacoff, Rachel, 1983, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 765)
    - Jaffé, William, 1967, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 766)
    - James, Thomas, 1970-80 (Box 21, Folder 767)
    - James Agee Film Project, 1975-79 (Box 21, Folder 768)
    - Jan, William, 1977-81 (Box 21, Folder 769)
    - Jarrell, Mary, 1976-77, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 770)
    - Jarrell, Randall, 1948-53 (Box 21, Folder 771)
    - Javitch, Daniel, 1976-84 (Box 21, Folder 772)
    - Javitch, Leila, 1968-84 (Box 21, Folder 773)
    - Jay, Peter, 1970-80 (Box 21, Folder 774)
    - Jenkins, John Holmes, 1970 Jan 26 (Box 21, Folder 775)
    - John Berryman Studies, 1975 Nov 16 (Box 21, Folder 776)
    - John D. and Catherine T. MacArthur Foundation, 1981 (Box 21, Folder 777)
    - John Hancock Mutual Life Insurance Company, 1981-82, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 778)
    - John Simon Guggenheim Memorial Foundation, 1952-84, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 779-780)
    - Johns Hopkins University, 1975-77, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 781)
    - Johnson, Carol, 1967-71 (Box 21, Folder 782)
      Includes review
    - Johnson, Tom, 1982 Jun 6 (Box 21, Folder 783)
    - Johnston, Carl, 1978-84 (Box 21, Folder 784-785)
      Includes copies of manuscript
    - Jonathan Edwards College (Yale University), 1983-84 (Box 21, Folder 786)
    - Jones, Alan, 1975 Mar 25 (Box 21, Folder 787)
    - Jordan, Norman, 1973 Jul 30 (Box 21, Folder 788)
    - Josipovici, Gabriel, 1977-79 (Box 21, Folder 789)
    - Jubilee, 1962 (Box 21, Folder 790)
    - "K" General, 1950-81, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 791)
    - Kaiser, Walter, 1969-82 (Box 21, Folder 792)
    - Kamb, Barclay, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 793)
    - Kaplan, Bernard, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 794)
    - Kaplan, Norman, 1977 Dec 5 (Box 21, Folder 795)
    - Karmel, Pepe, 1977-79 (Box 21, Folder 796)
    - Kaufman, Walter, 1964 May 23 (Box 21, Folder 797)
    - Kazan, Elia, 1964 (Box 21, Folder 798)
    - Keck, Caroline K., n.d. (Box 22, Folder 799)
    - Keefe, Tom, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 800)
    - Keeley, Edmund, 1958-84, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 801)
    - Kelleher, John V., 1976-77 (Box 22, Folder 802)
      Includes carbon copy of letter from Kelleher to Thomas Heffernan
    - Kennedy, Karen, 1969 Jul 30 (Box 22, Folder 803)
    - Kennedy, Kevin Edward, 1979-80 (Box 22, Folder 804)
    - Kent State University, 1974-75 (Box 22, Folder 805)
    - The Kenyon Review, 1938-83, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 806)
    - Ker, Alan, 1957-60 (Box 22, Folder 807)
    - Kerr, Walter, 1951-74 (Box 22, Folder 808)
    - Kidder, Tracy, 1966-74 (Box 22, Folder 809)
    - Kiely, Robert; Kiely, Jana, 1970-76 (Box 22, Folder 810)
    - Kinnell, Galway, 1980 (Box 22, Folder 811)
    - Kistler, William, 1971 May 9 (Box 22, Folder 812)
    - Kizer, Carolyn, 1961-79 (Box 22, Folder 813)
    - Klappert, Peter, 1973-84 (Box 22, Folder 814)
      Includes copies of writings and application
    - Klein, Cornelis, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 815)
    - Klopfer, Donald, 1972 Feb 21 (Box 22, Folder 816)
    - Konner, Melvin
      Related Materials
      See: Writings of Others, Konner, Melvin, Box 75, folder 2643
    - Knapp, Jean, 1964-65 (Box 22, Folder 817)
    - Knapp, Peter, 1964-66 (Box 22, Folder 818)
    - Kramer, Victor, 1975-84 (Box 22, Folder 819)
      Includes copies of material relating to James Agee
    - Kreisberg, Sanford, 1978-84 (Box 22, Folder 820)
      Includes writings
    - Kronenberger, Louis; Kronenberger, Emily, 1949 Dec 29 (Box 22, Folder 821)
    - Kunitz, Stanley, 1973-74 (Box 22, Folder 822)
    - Kuusisto, Stephen, 1981 Jan 8 (Box 22, Folder 823)
    - "L" General, 1951-84, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 824)
    - Lane, Edward H., 1980 (Box 22, Folder 825)
    - Langland, Joseph, 1961-62 (Box 22, Folder 826)
    - Lant, Jeffrey L, 1979-82 (Box 22, Folder 827)
    - Larrabee, Harold A., 1953 (Box 22, Folder 828)
      Includes draft of manuscript
      See also: Sarah Lawrence College, Box 33, folder 1259
    - Larsson, Raymond E. F., 1939 (Box 22, Folder 829)
    - Lattimore, Alice, 1984, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 830)
    - Lattimore, Richard, 1982 Jun 21 (Box 22, Folder 831)
    - Laughlin, Anne, 1966-84 (Box 22, Folder 832)
    - Laughlin, James, 1933-84 (Box 23, Folder 833-840)
      See also: New Directions Publishing, Corp., Box 28, folders 1051-1052 and Writings of Others, Laughlin, James, Box 75, folders 2655-2659
    - Laughlin, James, 1984, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 841-842)
    - Laughlin, Paul, 1976 Oct 24 (Box 23, Folder 843)
    - Laurie, Peter, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 844)
    - LaVerdiere, William, 1947-65, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 845)
    - Lawner, Lynne, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 846)
    - Lawry, Robert P., 1975-77 (Box 23, Folder 847)
    - League of American Writers, 1938 Feb 1 (Box 23, Folder 848)
    - LeBaron, Charles, 1982-84 (Box 23, Folder 849)
    - LeClaire, Cynthia, 1984 Dec 4 (Box 23, Folder 850)
    - Lee, [A. S. (Alewyn S.)?], n.d. (Box 23, Folder 851)
    - Lee, Laurie, 1957 Jul 30 (Box 23, Folder 852)
    - Leethauser, Brad, 1981, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 853)
    - Leger, Dorothy, 1966-78 (Box 23, Folder 854)
    - Lemann, Thomas B., 1974-81 (Box 23, Folder 855)
    - Leone, John, 1969-71 (Box 23, Folder 856)
    - Leoni, Francesca, 1960 Oct 22 (Box 23, Folder 857)
    - Lester, Valerie, 1981-84 (Box 23, Folder 858)
    - Levertov, Denise, 1963 Dec 10 (Box 23, Folder 859)
    - Levi, Peter
      See: Personal Papers, Speaking Engagements, Box 104, folder 3590
    - Levien, Stephen, 1982 May 17 (Box 24, Folder 860)
    - LeVillain, Henriette, 1975-82, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 861)
    - Levin, Harry, 1967-83 (Box 24, Folder 862)
    - Levin, Richard, 1984 Nov 20 (Box 24, Folder 863)
    - Levine, Philip, 1982 Mar 19 (Box 24, Folder 864)
    - Lewis, R. W. B. (Richard Warrington Baldwin, 1983 Feb 27 (Box 24, Folder 865)
    - L'Heureux, John, 1984 (Box 24, Folder 866)
    - Library of Congress, 1949-84, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 867)
    - Library of the Boston Athenaeum, 1982 Apr 13 (Box 24, Folder 868)
    - Lida, Denah, 1967 Jul (Box 24, Folder 869)
    - Lindbeck, John M. H., 1946 Apr 12 (Box 24, Folder 870)
    - Lindsay, Elizabeth Connor, 1931-37, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 871)
    - Lindsay, Nick, 1978 May 20 (Box 24, Folder 872)
    - Lindsay, Vachel, 1930-31 (Box 24, Folder 873)
    - Lish, Gordon, 1981, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 874)
    - Literary Research Newsletter, 1976 Jan 16 (Box 24, Folder 875)
    - Locher, Kaspar T., 1962-63 (Box 24, Folder 876)
    - Logan, John, 1953-55 (Box 24, Folder 877)
    - Longstreth, Bevis; Longstreth, Clara, 1965, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 878)
    - Lord, George de Forest, 1974-80 (Box 24, Folder 879)
    - Lord, Ruth, 1976-79 (Box 24, Folder 880)
    - Louisiana State University Press (Baton Rouge, L.A.), 1973-80 (Box 24, Folder 881)
    - Lowe, Elizabeth, 1973 Aug 2 (Box 24, Folder 882)
    - Lowell, Robert, 1948-64, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 883)
    - Loyola University of Chicago, 1976 (Box 24, Folder 884)
    - Lubin, Peter, 1967-74, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 885)
    - Luce, Henry R., 1942-49 (Box 24, Folder 886)
    - Lucy Kroll Agency, 1983-85 (Box 24, Folder 887)
    - Lurie, Allison, 1979 Jul 17 (Box 24, Folder 888)
    - Lurie, Carol, 1977-81 (Box 24, Folder 889)
    - Lyman, Daniel, 1973, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 890)
    - Lynch, Larry, 1975-78, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 891)
    - Lytle, Andrew, 1961-62 (Box 24, Folder 892)
    - "M" General, 1939-81, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 893-894)
    - Maas, Willard, 1934 (Box 24, Folder 895)
    - McCann, David, 1974-79 (Box 24, Folder 896)
    - McCarthy, Eugene, 1977 Apr 20 (Box 24, Folder 897)
    - McCarthy, Sandy, 1977-84 (Box 24, Folder 898)
    - Macauley, Robie, 1981 Oct 7 (Box 24, Folder 899)
    - McCord, David, 1974-84 (Box 24, Folder 900)
    - MacDonald, Dwight, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 901)
    - McDougal, Stuart Y., 1973-84 (Box 24, Folder 902)
    - McDowell, David, 1970-78, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 903)
      See also: Crown Publishers, Box 8, folder 319
    - MacDowell Colony, Inc., 1935-83, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 904)
      Includes newsletter
    - McDowell, Obolensky Inc., 1958 Feb. (Box 25, Folder 905)
    - McGara, Bonnie, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 906)
    - McGarrell, Ann, 1970, 1973 (Box 25, Folder 907)
    - McGovern, George S., 1980 Mar (Box 25, Folder 908)
    - McGraw-Hill Book Company, 1970 Apr 23 (Box 25, Folder 909)
    - McHugh, Heather, 1974, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 910)
    - Mack, John E., 1974 Mar 15 (Box 25, Folder 911)
    - Mackaye, Percy, 1939 (Box 25, Folder 912)
    - McLaughlin, J. M., 1943-44, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 913)
    - MacLeish, Archibald, 1933-79, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 914)
    - MacLeod, Norman, 1974 Dec 27 (Box 25, Folder 915)
    - MacLeon, Robert, 1977 Sep 7 (Box 25, Folder 916)
    - McMaster, Helen, 1953 (Box 25, Folder 917)
    - MacMillan Company, 1964-65 (Box 25, Folder 918)
    - McRae, Betty; McRae, William C., 1970-71, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 919)
    - Maddow, Ben, 1964 Feb 18 (Box 25, Folder 920)
    - Mademoiselle, 1970-78 (Box 25, Folder 921)
      Includes foreword to Flannery O'Connor's The Crop
    - Madison Avenue Presbyterian (New York, N.Y.), 1951 Jan 6 (Box 25, Folder 922)
    - Madsen, Steve, 1973-77 (Box 25, Folder 923)
      Includes copies of poems and recommendation letters
    - Mahony, Medb, 1975-78 (Box 25, Folder 924)
    - Mailer, Norman, 1977 Mar 18 (Box 25, Folder 925)
      Includes draft of press statement
    - Makowsky, Veronica A., 1984 (Box 25, Folder 926)
    - Malahat Review, 1975 (Box 25, Folder 927)
    - Malamud, Bernard; Malamud, Ann, 1971 Dec 3 (Box 25, Folder 928)
    - Malan, Jacques, 1961-70 (Box 25, Folder 929)
    - Malanga, Gerard, 1973 (Box 25, Folder 930)
    - Malone, Michael; Quilligan, Maureen, 1977-84 (Box 25, Folder 931)
    - Mancini, Joseph, 1973-82 (Box 25, Folder 932)
    - Mangan, Mary, 1939-40, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 933)
    - Mangan, Sherry, 1931-43, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 934-936)
    - Mansfield, John, 1971, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 937)
    - Mansfield, Richard A., n.y. Jun 24 (Box 25, Folder 938)
      Includes clippings
    - Manufacturer's Hanover Trust Company, 1971 Jan (Box 25, Folder 939)
    - Mardersteig, Giovanni, 1959-72, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 940)
    - Margolis, R., 1973 (Box 25, Folder 941)
    - Marguerite S. Mason, Realtor, 1964 (Box 25, Folder 942)
    - Marichal, Juan, 1971-76, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 943)
    - Maritain, Jacques, 1950-81 (Box 25, Folder 944)
    - Marshall, John, 1961-62, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 945)
    - Marshall, Megan, 1977-84, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 946)
    - Martin, Frank, 1982 Jul (Box 25, Folder 947)
    - Martin, Jean-Claude, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 948)
    - Marx, Spencer, 1970-76 (Box 25, Folder 949)
    - Mary Roberts Reinhart Foundation, 1981 Jun 17 (Box 25, Folder 950)
    - Mason, Herbert, 1986 Aug 26 (Box 25, Folder 951)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology, 1971-76 (Box 25, Folder 952)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology. Dept. of Humanities, 1980-84 (Box 25, Folder 953)
    - Massola Family, 1959 (Box 25, Folder 954)
    - Masters, Dexter, 1984 Apr 3 (Box 25, Folder 955)
    - Matchett, William H., 1962-82 (Box 25, Folder 956)
    - Mathews, Jackson; Mathews, Marthiel, 1958-79 (Box 25, Folder 957)
    - Mattair, Peter, 1976-78 (Box 25, Folder 958)
    - Matthews [T. S. (Thomas Stanley)?], 1938-84 (Box 26, Folder 959-962)
      Includes poems and enclosures
    - Matthias, John, 1981 (Box 26, Folder 963)
    - Maxwell, Emily, 1947-84, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 964)
    - Maxwell, William, 1931-84, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 965-971)
      Includes photographs and enclosures
    - May, John R., 1975 Nov (Box 26, Folder 972)
    - Mazzarins, Laimdota, 1969-76 (Box 26, Folder 973)
    - Menasce, Jean de, 1956 Mar (Box 26, Folder 974)
    - Mendelson, Edward, 1976-82 (Box 26, Folder 975)
    - Merchants National Bank of Boston (Boston, Mass.), 1968-74 (Box 26, Folder 976)
    - Meredeth, William, 1977, 1984 (Box 26, Folder 977)
    - Merideth, Robert, 1965 Apr 19 (Box 26, Folder 978)
      Includes copy of poem by Bernard Strempek
    - Merindal, Jacques Malon de, 1958-62 (Box 26, Folder 979)
    - Merrill, James, 1977-83 (Box 26, Folder 980)
    - Mespoulet, M. (Marguerite), 1943-56, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 981)
    - Metzdorf, Robert [Frederic?], 1974 Jun 23 (Box 26, Folder 982)
    - Meyers, Jeffrey, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 983)
    - Mezzasomma, Guido, 1970-71 (Box 26, Folder 984)
    - Miami University, 1975 Feb 11 (Box 26, Folder 985)
    - Mihanovich, Clement Simon, 1982 Oct 6 (Box 26, Folder 986)
    - Milano, Paolo, 1975 Apr 9 (Box 26, Folder 987)
    - Miller, Arthur, 1984 Aug 29 (Box 26, Folder 988)
    - Miller, Henry, n.y. Jan 19 (Box 26, Folder 989)
    - Miller, William, 1954-65 (Box 26, Folder 990-991)
    - Mills, M. (Marguerite), 1964-76, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 992)
    - Milson, Toby, 1972-73 (Box 27, Folder 993)
    - Milton Academy (Milton, Mass.), 1977 Dec 13 (Box 27, Folder 994)
    - Mizener, Arthur, 1953 (Box 27, Folder 995)
    - Modern Age, 1979 Jul 28 (Box 27, Folder 996)
    - Modern Poetry Association, 1984 May 15 (Box 27, Folder 997)
    - Moholy-Nagy, László, 1938 Sep 18 (Box 27, Folder 998)
    - Mojtabai, A. G., 1976-80, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 999)
    - Moldlaw, Carol, 1979-84, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 1000)
    - Montale, Mosca, 1960 (Box 27, Folder 1001)
    - Moore, G. E. (Geoffrey Edward), 1932 Jun 19 (Box 27, Folder 1002)
    - Moore, Geoffrey, 1971 Apr 30 (Box 27, Folder 1003)